tutorius.net 2010-06-10

# Privacy Policy - Free Tutorial and Design Idea on tutorius.net

What follows is the Privacy Statement for all Tutorius websites including all the websites run under the http://www.tutorius.net. Please read this statement regarding our blogs. If you have questions please ask us via our contact form.

Email Address  
You may choose to add your email address to our contact list via the forms on our websites. We agree that we will never share you email with any third party and that we will remove your email at your request. We don’t currently send advertising via email, but in the future our email may contain advertisements and we may send dedicated email messages from our advertisers without revealing your email addresses to them. If you have any problem removing your email address please contact us via our contact form.

Cookies and Web Beacons  
www.tutorius.net does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site such as Google (www.google.com/adsense) that use the DART cookie enables that place ads on our web site. For further information, consult the privacy policy of each those websites. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. To opt out of Google’s use of cookies, please visit the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.tutorius.net/?rb_uQvyI "Original Link: http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html")

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.tutorius.net send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. www.tutorius.net has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.tutorius.nets’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

Disclaimer  
www.tutorius.net also provides you collection of links to other websites containing PDF tutorial / manuals ebook and other information that compile in pdf format. We merely take the power of Google Search Engine to find those materials and link to it. None of those materials are hosted in this server Nor uploaded by me in Someone’s server.

If you are owner of the site of any links provided on this site and wants to remove your link from our site then please Contact us with our Email to tutoriusdotnet (at) gmail.com subjected “Remove Links from www.tutorius.net”.

We are neither affiliated with authors and brands nor responsible for its content and change of content. Products and names mentioned are the property of their respective owners. Tutorius.net are NOT affiliated with the products and/ or names mentioned in this site. This site consists of a compilation of public information available on the internet.

Information contained on Tutorius.net is provided “as is” without warranty of any kind, either expressed or implied, including any warranty of merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose. In no event shall ANYONE be held liable for any loss of profit, special, incidental, consequential, or other similar claims.
